(My Comment)
(My other comment)
According to the prophecy. . .`
. . .the stallion will ride
to the ends of the earth.
The earth ends at the black salt sea.
No horse can cross the poison water.
The earth does not end at the sea. . .
. . .there are many dirts beyond the sea.
The dirt where I was born.
Not dirts. Lands.
Lands, yes. . .
There are thousands of ships
in the free cities.
Wooden horses that fly across the sea. . .
Let's speak no more of wooden horses
and iron chairs.
It's not a chair. It's a. . .
A chair for a King to sit upon,
or. . .
. . .a Queen.
A King does not need a chair to sit upon.
He only needs a horse.
Sweet reds. . .
I have sweet reds from Lys,
Volantis and the Arbor!
Tyroshi pear brandy! Andalish sours!
I have them! I have them!
A taste for the Khaleesi?
I have a sweet red from Dorne, my lady.
One taste and you'II
name your first child after me.
Put down that cask.
Moon of my life.
Are you hurt?
Jorah the Andal,
I heard what you did.
Choose any horse you wish, it is yours.
I make this gift to you.
And to my son,
the stallion who will mount the world,
I will also pledge a gift.
I will give him the iron chair. . .
. . .that his mother's father sat upon.
I will give him Seven Kingdoms.
I, Drogo, will do this.
I will take my Khalasar west
to where the worId ends. . .
. . .and ride wooden horses
across the black salt water. . .
- . . .as no Khal has done before.
- (Men cheering)
I will kill the men in iron suits. . .
- (Cheering)
- (Still Cheering)
- I will rape their women. . .
- (Cheering)
- (Cheering even more!!)
. . .take their children as slaves. . .
. . .and bring their broken gods
back to Vaes Dothrak.
This, I vow. . .
. . . I, Drogo, son of Bharbo.
I swear before the Mother of Mountains. . .
. . .as the stars look down in witness.
As the stars look down in witness.
(BLAH)